Our colleague Ashish Upmany has
joined to tell us which stocks will see action today based on the news. Ashish, tell us which
news will impact the stocks today. Let's
talk about Updater Services. It is a
recently listed entity, so 7.2%
equity was locked in. Now these shareholders will be
able to sell these shares in the open market, so
perhaps some selling pressure may be seen in this counter.
Keep your eye on Updater Services. Apart from this,
keep an eye on Snowman Logistics. The
promoters have bought an additional stake.
Talking about yesterday's block deal, Gateway
Distri Parks, which is the promoter
entity of the company, has bought approximately 4 lakh
equity shares through open market
transactions. Due to this,
action may be seen in this stock as well.
Apart from this, let's also look at Med Plus.
Some negative action is seen coming
where the company has received orders from the Assistant Director and
Drug Sales Licensing Authority. The
company has some stores, there are three
stores for which suspension orders have been received.  The
temporary suspension is for three to seven
days, but some negative action may be
seen on this counter as well.
ICICI Lombard General
Insurance has
received a show-cost-cum-demand notice for a tax
demand of ₹
1,728 crore, along with a
penalty of ₹173 crore. Therefore, there is a
significant demand, so negative action
may be seen on this counter as well.
Phoenix Mills has
also received a show-cost-cum-demand notice from the GST authority for ₹
2.73 crore.
Negative action may be
seen on this counter as well.
Swan Energy has also
informed exchanges about some fundraising plans, stating that it has
approved the fundraising. The
fundraising has been approved by a QIP (Qualified Inventory)
and is worth ₹4,000 crore. So,
keep an eye on Swan Energy as well. Lemon Tree Hotels, meanwhile, has
some expansion plans.  Plans are coming to light
where the company has
signed a franchise. A
new hotel of the company may come up in Uttarakhand, so some
expansion plans can be seen here.
Apart from this, remember Ugra Capital has been
in focus for the last few days
and has been a big wealth creator. This stock is
again having a board of directors meeting today
where fund raising plans will be considered. So,
due to these fund raising plans, we will
see action in this stock as well.
Okay, thank you Shisha
for sharing all this information. So, this stock will be
in focus today due to the news.